The Knights have done the impossible,
rising all the way from the bottom of the league
to the Final Four,
under head coach
Ted Vincent!
Meanwhile, the Eagles, once a top contender
for the championship,
have suffered
four straight losses.
Losers! Go home!
You're a damn disgrace!
Idiots!
You can't even
win against
the worst teams
in the league!
And you!
Your plays get worse every damn game.
How are we supposed to win a title like that?
Why is it that the moment
I stopped using
Ted's plays,
nothing works anymore?
Boss,
we just got careless
these last few games.
Don't worry.
We're gonna crush them next game.
Oh, right.
Next game, the semifinals against the Knights.
You lose that,
every fucking
one of you is fired.
So we are here
in the locker room
with Knights' coach, Ted!
Wait a second,
isn't that our former assistant coach?